我和我的兄弟姊妹是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
KLAUS: My siblings and I are the first
vampires in all of history.
是真祖家族
The original family.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
Three centuries ago,
we helped build a town,
这个城市
called New Orleans.
现在女巫密谋将我引回此地
Now, a plot by witches
has lured me back,
希望我能打败一个暴君
hoping that I will defeat a tyrant.
一个我所创造的吸血鬼
A vampire I created.
我哥哥希望透过家庭的力量
My brother hopes
I will find redemption
让我得到救赎
透过一个奇迹般的孩子
through the power of family,
a miracle child.
半狼人半吸血鬼
Part werewolf, part vampire.
一个混合种
A hybrid.
我妹妹心怀疑虑
My sister is doubtful.
她觉得我无可救药了
She thinks I am beyond redemption.
尽管我哥哥做了最大的努力
我却有自己的打算
Despite my brother's best efforts,
I have a plan of my own.
我会夺回我的家园
让它重新属于我
I will take back my home
and reclaim what was mine.
我会成为王
I will be king.
纽奥良
MAN 2: The city of New Orleans.
全国各地形形色色的人们
People of all stripes and flavors,
from all over the country,
来到这里参加我们在街上的派对
come here to party on our streets.
有些只是来找找乐子
Some are just looking for fun.
有些则是为了寻求更加阴暗
更加危险的事情
Some are looking for something
a little darker... more dangerous.
所有我们邀请他们来到我家
我们可以满足他们
So, we invite them into my home
and we give it to them.
（屠宰场
派对永不结束〕
午夜来临，一切都会改变
Then, at the stroke of midnight,
everything changes.
是吸血的时候了
And it's time to feed.
这就是我让我的人开心的方法
This is how I keep my guys happy.
一个尽情享用的自助场合
The occasional
all-you-can-eat buffet.
我的夜行者很喜欢
My Nightwalkers love it.
他们得非常努力才能得到一枚日光戒指
Got 'em working hard, trying to
earn one of these daylight rings.
他们得释放一些精力
They deserve to blow off
a little steam.
我信任的那几个日行者
他们很喜欢派对
My Daywalkers, the trusted few?
They just like to party.
还真是声势浩大啊
It's quite an operation.
那你说说，那些被吸血的人怎么办？
Tell me, what about the victims?
似乎得挖很多坟墓才够
Seems like a lot of graves to dig.
不能全杀光
Can't kill 'em all.
太多人失踪，旅游业会受损
Too many folks go missing,
tourism drops.
所以我们会用一点吸血鬼血来治愈他们
So, we heal 'em
with a little vamp blood...
抹掉记忆，再送他们上路
...erase their memory,
send 'em on their way.
没混乱，没烦恼
No muss, no fuss.
真有一套
I'm impressed.
都是从你那里学到的招数
Nothin' I didn't learn from you,
back in the day.
马赛尔
Marcel.
什么事，提艾里？
What's up, Thierry?
我们有六个人
在法语区外的一间酒吧被杀了
Six of our guys were killed
in a bar outside of the Quarter.
夜行者
Nightwalkers.
没人看到是谁干的
No one saw who.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：夺回家园
以利亚
Elijah?
如果不接电话
是你引我回这个该死城市的
If not answering your phone is part
of your clever plan to get me back to
聪明计划的一部分
那么干得好
this godforsaken city,
then, well done.
因为我很担心
约瑟夫摩根
I'm here and I'm worried.
在我踢开你该死的大门之前快接电话
Now, pick up,
before I kick in your bloody door.
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
你是谁啊？
Who the hell are you?
你是女佣吧
主演：克莱儿荷特
Ah, you must be the maid.
我的包包在车上，帮我拿来
主演：克莱儿荷特
My bags are in the car.
Get them, will you?
嘿，我不是女佣
Hello.
Not the maid.
对
Right.
你是被我哥哥克劳斯搞大肚子的狼女
主演：菲比托金
You're that werewolf girl
my brother, Klaus, knocked up.
我还想着会看到…
I was expecting to see
…超自然的神奇大肚子呢
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
some kind
of supernatural, miracle baby-bump.
看来还没显现出来
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Guess you're not showing, yet.
你是海莉，对吧？
It's Hayley, isn't it?
你跟你哥一样没礼貌
You have your brother's manners.
还有他的臭脾气，所以小心点
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
And his temper, too.
So, watch it.
以利亚呢？
主演：莉雅派普斯
Where's Elijah?
问倒我了
主演：莉雅派普斯
Beats me.
他消失很久了
He's long gone.
“消失很久”是什么意思？
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
What do you mean, "long gone?"
前一秒还在这里
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
Well, one minute, he was here,
信誓旦旦地承诺要保护我
making
epic promises about protecting me,
因为一瓶苏格兰威士忌
in this predicament
that a bottle of scotch
和糟糕的决定让我陷入窘境
and some bad decisions got me into.
他诗情画意地描述着我们是一家人
He was all poetic
about how we're family.
然后克劳斯就告诉我他跑了
And then, Klaus told me he bailed.
看来这就是我信任吸血鬼的下场
Guess that's what I get,
for trusting a vampire.
以利亚不是什么普通的吸血鬼
他从不违背诺言
Elijah is not just any vampire
and he doesn't break promises.
这就说明尼克劳斯做了典型的…
制片：兰斯安德森
Which means Niklaus has done
…他风格的卑鄙事
something dastardly and Klaus-like.
克劳斯，滚出来
告诉我你对我们哥哥做了什么
Klaus! Get out here and tell me
what you've done with our brother,
你这个自恋阴险的小人
you narcissistic,
backstabbing wanker!
喊够了吧
Enough with all the shouting.
妹妹，我该想到的
Little sister, I should have known.
我想那六个吸血鬼是你杀的吧
I assume the six dead
vampires were your doing.
他们太无礼了
They were very rude.
想要伤害一个可怜无辜的女孩
Trying to victimize a poor,
innocent girl,
她只不过是想要去法语区
just trying to find
her way to the Quarter.
抱歉，他们是你的朋友吗？
So sorry, were they friends of yours?
对了，你没朋友的
That's right,
you don't have any friends.
我有朋友，我有马赛尔
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
I do have friends.
I have Marcel.
你记得他吧？
You remember him, don't you?
你当然记得
Yes, of course you do.
他现在自封为法语区的国王
He fancies himself
the king of the Quarter,
关于杀死吸血鬼，他有一些规矩
and he has these
rules about killing vampires.
看看他对你会有怎样的处罚
会很有趣的
It'll be fun to see what sort of
punishment he comes up with for you.
我不在乎马赛尔，还有他的规矩
I don't care about Marcel
or his rules.
以利亚不会失信
你对他做了什么？
Elijah doesn't welsh on deals.
What did you do to him?
也许他在度假
编剧：黛安艾德穆强，戴克兰迪巴拉
Perhaps he's on holiday.
或者在楼上陷入长长的秋睡
Or taking a long,
autumn nap, upstairs.
去啊，四处看看
Well, go on.
Take a look around.
导演：布烈德特纳尔
你和我一样都还熟悉这屋子
You remember this house as well as l.
我记得一切
I remember everything.
(1820年 纽奥良）
我记得那个总是醉醺醺的
傻瓜州长是如何
WOMAN: I remember how the drunken fool
of a governor hid away
掩盖我们吸血鬼的罪行换取金子的
all of our vampire sins,
in exchange for gold.
我记得州长举办的奢华派对
I remember the lavish parties
the governor threw,
似乎是为了讨好你
as if to impress you.
我记得有一刻
I remember finding
a moment of affection
我爱上了州长的儿子艾米尔
with the governor's son, Emil.
我记得甚至连以利亚都过得很快乐
And I remember that
even Elijah was happy.
你弟弟，他太过分了
Your brother, he's gone too far.
尼克劳斯，你真的没救了，是吧？
Niklaus, there is no
hope for you, is there?
- 我们打扰到你们了吗？
- 是的
-Are we interrupting?
-Yes.
没有
No.
亲爱的以利亚
你希望我得到幸福
Dearest Elijah, you've only
ever wished happiness for me.
我和艾米尔恋爱了
Emil and I are in love.
请允许我把他变成吸血鬼
Please, let me turn him.
蕾贝卡，州长仁慈地同意
Rebekah, the governor
has graciously agreed
掩盖我们许多…不适宜的行为
to hide a lot of our indiscretions.
但绝不会同意把他唯一的儿子
变成和我们一样
It would not do to turn
his only son into one of us.
为了我，求求你了
Please.
For me.
不可能的，妹妹
It's not gonna happen, sister.
如果我们把每个
和你睡的男人都变成吸血鬼
If we turned every man you
dropped your knickers for,
那么人类就会不复存在了
我们就没有血可喝了
then, human beings would cease to
exist and we'd have no bloody food.
你竟敢说这样的话，先生？
How dare you, sir?
- 你最好…
- 尼克劳斯，弟弟
-You would do well to--
-Niklaus. Brother.
尼克劳斯
Niklaus!
- 等等
- 不要
-Wait!
-No!
他配不上你
Well, he wasn't good enough for you.
从来没有人能配得上我，尼克
你尽力确保了这一点
No one was ever good enough for me,
Nik, you made sure of that.
以利亚在哪？
Now, where is Elijah?
你去哪？
Where are you going?
看来夜晚还没完全结束
It appears the night
is not quite over, yet.
我要去和马赛尔再喝一杯
I'm off for another drink
with Marcel.
以利亚告诉了我你的逐步摧毁
Elijah told me your plan to take
apart Marcel's empire,
马赛尔帝国的计划
piece by piece.
我不记得计划里有你们俩
一起把纽奥良喝干
I don't remember it involving you two
drinking New Orleans dry, together.
我知道你没什么朋友，蕾贝卡
I know you don't have
many friends, Rebekah.
但是有些朋友在一起时会喝酒
But what some friends do, when they
get together, is they drink.
喝酒的时候，他们就会说出秘密
And when they drink,
they tell secrets.
马赛尔找到了办法控制
法语区的所有女巫
Marcel has, somehow, found a way
to control the entirety of witches
我打算搞清楚原因
in the Quarter and I aim
to uncover the how,
这样我就能加以利用
so I might take it for myself.
找到以利亚并不是我今天要做的事
Finding Elijah didn't
make my to-do list, today.
对了，欢迎回家，妹妹
Oh, and welcome home, little sister.
你，狼女
You. Wolf-girl.
我要一寸一寸搜遍整间房子
I'm gonna search this house,
inch-by-inch,
直到找到我的坏哥哥
到底对好哥哥做了什么
until I find what my evil brother
has done to my good one.
你来帮忙
You're helping.
州长有许多密室
The governor had
lots of secret rooms.
我带你看看他最爱的一间
I'll show you his favorite.
你觉得克劳斯杀了他
You think Klaus killed him.
我们是杀不死的，傻女孩
We can't be killed, silly girl.
但那也不能阻止克劳斯
想方法设法折磨我们
That doesn't stop Klaus from
finding ways to torture us.
他有一套神秘的银匕首
He has a set of mystical,
silver daggers.
一旦插入心脏就能让我们沉睡过去
One in the heart sends us
into a deep slumber.
克劳斯喜欢把我们装进棺材
Klaus gets his jollies
from keeping us in a box,
直到他决定把匕首拔出来
until he decides to
pull the dagger out.
他一定是这么对付以利亚的
That must be what
he's done to Elijah.
这个是我的
This one's mine.
他随时准备着你的棺材
He keeps your coffin on standby.
他喜欢做好准备
以防他的家人
He likes to be prepared
for when his family members,
让他失望
inevitably, disappoint him.
以利亚的棺材不在这里
他一定把他藏在别处了
Elijah's isn't here.
He must have stashed him elsewhere.
我感觉好恶心
I feel sick.
欢迎加入真祖家族，亲爱的
Welcome to the family, love.
你一发现以利亚不见就该逃走的
You should have run, the second
you realized Elijah was gone.
是啊，但女巫在我身上下咒了
Yeah, well, the witches have
put some sort of hex on me.
只要我怀着这个孩子
就不能离开纽奥良
As long as I'm carrying this baby,
I can't leave New Orleans.
一旦这么做，她们会杀了我
If I do, they kill me.
我了解克劳斯，一旦你生下肚子里
Knowing Klaus,
he's planning a box for you,
那个不知什么的东西
他就会替你准备棺材了
the second you give birth to
whatever's cooking in your tum.
我一我到以利亚就走
I'm leaving,
as soon as I find Elijah.
数十年插着匕首躺在棺材里糟糕透了
Being daggered in a
box for decades sucks.
相信我
Trust me.
你最好想办法破除咒语逃走
You best find a way
to break that hex and run.
有人吗？
Hello?
不是吧，马赛尔
Seriously, Marcel?
想吓唬我吗？
Trying to scare me?
昨晚你的人被杀跟我毫无关系
I had nothing to do with
the attack on your guys last night!
苏菲德弗罗
Sophie Deveraux.
我哥哥以利亚跟我提过你
My brother, Elijah,
told me about you.
知道我是谁吗？
Know who I am?
嗯，知道
Yeah, I know.
那你知道我们该好好谈谈了
Then, you know I need to talk.
要我猜的话，根据克劳斯过去的作为
So, if I had to guess,
knowing Klaus' history,
以利亚现在胸口插着匕首
Elijah has a dagger in his chest.
那是个魔法物
你是女巫
It's a magical object.
You're a witch.
施个定位咒
找到匕首就能找到以利亚
Do a locator spell,
locate the dagger, locate Elijah.
我不能使用魔法
这是死罪
I can't use magic.
It's punishable by death.
- 马赛尔的规矩
- 马赛尔？
-Marcel's rules.
-Marcel?
你觉得如果你不能给我我想要的
What do you think
I'm going to do to you,
我会对你做什么呢？
if you don't give me what I want?
做不了什么
Not much.
我被连结了
I've been linked.
你对我做什么
就是对海莉做什么
So, anything you do to me,
you do to Hayley.
谁？
Who?
对了，怀孕的那个
Oh, right, the mumsy.
算你走运，以利亚似乎很在乎她
Well, luckily for you,
Elijah seems to care about her.
否则我现在就扭断你的脖子
Otherwise, I'd break your neck,
right here.
马赛尔怎么会有这么大能耐？
How did Marcel get
so bloody powerful, anyway?
我一百年前离开时可不是这样的
He wasn't like this when I left
a hundred years ago.
马赛尔有办法知道
有人在法语区使用魔法
Marcel has a way to tell whenever
there's magic done in the Quarter.
他是怎么做到的并不重要
The how isn't relevant.
我告诉你什么不重要
I'll tell you
what's not bloody relevant.
一群不能使用魔法的女巫
A coven of witches
who can't do magic.
我的主意是，搬走吧
Here's an idea, move away.
我们习得的是祖传魔法
We practice ancestral magic.
这片墓地都是我们祖先的遗体
This cemetery is filled with
the remains of our witch ancestors.
不能接近他们，我们就没有能力
Without access to them,
we're powerless.
如果我们逃走
我们就抛弃了遗赠
If we run,
we're leaving our legacy behind.
我们的家、我们的家人
Our home, our family.
家人可没那么重要
Well, family's overrated.
看看我
我回到一个只带给我心痛的城市
Look at me, I'm back in a city
that's given me nothing but heartache,
寻找下决心保护一个孩子的哥哥
Iooking for a brother
who's hell-bent on protecting a baby
我根本不在乎那孩子
I don't care about.
很难相信
I find that hard to believe.
- 你还是来了
- 我是为以利亚而来
-You're here, aren't you?
-I'm here for Elijah.
一找到他，我立刻走
The instant I find him, I'm gone.
他傻乎乎地相信
He was the one who
idiotically believed this baby
这个孩子会是尼克劳斯的救赎
would be Niklaus' redemption.
而现在他失踪了，大概是克劳斯所为
And now, he's missing,
probably at the hands of Klaus himself.
而你傻得可以，居然相信
以利亚可以说服克劳斯
You were foolish enough to believe
that Elijah could convince Klaus
对付马赛尔
大家都知道他俩的过去
to go against Marcel, when everyone
knows that they have a history.
- 我知道克劳斯和马赛尔是父子关系
- 你不懂
-Klaus sired Marcel, I'm aware.
-You don't understand.
马赛尔不是随便什么
克劳斯转变成吸血鬼的人
Marcel is not just some guy
that Klaus turned into a vampire.
克劳斯把他当儿子一样疼爱
Klaus loved him like a son.
他们相遇的那天我也在
REBEKAH:
I was there the day that they met.
我们去埋葬艾米尔，州长的独子
We were burying Emil,
the governor's only son.
我们是这么以为的
Or so we thought.
结果发现州长还有一个儿子
It turns out,
the governor had another son,
是和他的一个奴隶所生
from a mother that he owned.
你叫什么名字？
What is your name?
我没有名字
Don't got one.
妈妈想要等到我十岁才给我取名
她怕我会死于热病
Mama wouldn't name me, 'til l
turned ten. Case the fever took me.
结果她却得热病死了
Then it took her.
你是个幸存者
You're a survivor.
幸存者需要名字
And survivors need names.
马赛勒斯怎么样？
How 'bout Marcellus?
马赛勒斯？
Marcellus?
来自于玛尔斯，战争之神
It comes from Mars, the god of war.
意思是“小战士”
And it means, "little warrior".
看来我们的兄弟还是有救的
Perhaps there is hope
for our brother, after all.
克劳斯在那个男孩身上看到了自己
Klaus saw himself in the boy.
他想起了我们父亲以前是怎么打他的
He remembered how our
father used to beat him.
他也是个私生子，而父亲就当他
He, too, was the bastard child
of a man who saw him as nothing
是头畜生
but a beast.
这就是为什么你的计划不会成功
And that is why your plan will fail.
你所做的只是把两个
迷失已久的灵魂凑在一起
All you've done is bring back together
two long-lost souls.
没有了以利亚
谁知道他们会做出什么事来？
Without Elijah between them,
who knows what they'll do?
这可比昨晚的派对差远了
Well, this is a far cry
from last night's party.
原来是想追卢梭酒吧的酒保啊
In pursuit of the bartender
from Rousseau's, I see.
正在努力
She's a work in progress.
你坐在这里为她消得人憔悴
And yet, here you are,
pining over her,
而没有拿她当午餐
when you should be
eating her for lunch.
她一定很特别
Well, she must be special.
先谈正事，验尸官打电话来了
Business, first.
The coroner called.
他有我的电话
万一出现进客的尸体就联系我
He's got my number,
in case any dead tourists show up.
让我精猜，手上盖着印记
Let me guess.
Dead tourists with a stamp on their hand
血管里有吸血鬼血的游客尸体
and vampire blood in their veins.
难免有意外嘛
有人喝醉失足摔下阳台
It happens. Someone takes
a drunken tumble off a balcony
或掉进密西西比河里
or into the Mississippi.
今天就有两具尸体需要处理
And today, I got two
of them to deal with.
打扰一下，亲爱的
你在念什么呢？
Excuse me, love.
What's that you're studying?
变态心理学
Abnormal psychology.
或许你可以帮我这位朋友诊断一下
Well, perhaps you can help me
diagnose my friend over here.
他最近有点情绪低落
He's been a little bit depressed.
老是在想一个女孩
Can't keep his mind off a girl.
他跟我说那女孩是配得上国王的王后
He tells me she's a queen,
fit for a king.
我认为他应该放手向前看
I think he should cut
his losses and move on.
你有什么专业意见？
What's your professional opinion?
做一个好人，或许机会
Be a nice guy,
and maybe the opportunity
就会找上门来
will present itself someday.
今晚怎么样？九点？
How about tonight?
Nine o'clock?
我就在这里等你
I'll meet you, right here?
我会考虑的
I'll take it under consideration.
强硬
Hm. Harsh.
看来我魅力不再了
I dare say, I've lost my touch.
或是你魅力不再了
Or you've lost yours.
等等
Oh, hey, hey.
打烊了，抱歉
We're closed, sorry.
我只需要一点点草药
拜托
I just need one teeny, tiny,
little herb. Please?
什么草药？
Which herb?
研磨好的附子花
Crushed aconite flower.
附子草？那可是毒药
Wolf's-bane?
That's a poison.
想要杀死哪个狼人吗？
Looking to kill a wolf?
只是一只小狼
Just a little one.
等我一下
Gimme a minute.
和曼陀罗混在一起，滴几滴在热茶里
Cut it with Jimson weed....
A few drops in some hot tea.
这样就行了
That should do it.
给你
Here.
狼人要在这城市生存很难
It's an ugly town for wolves.
你这么做是对的
You're doing the right thing.
嘿，想讨赏吗？
Hey, wanna gain points?
告诉马赛尔法语区有个狼人
Tell Marcel there's a werewolf
in the Quarter.
你带我来了个绝佳之地
KLAUS: You take me
to the nicest places.
欢迎来到死后的世界
Welcome to the land
of the newly-dead.
我就不浪费时间了
I won't waste your time.
我想你跟他们说明过情况了
I trust you filled them in.
说实话，这两个没什么潜力
To be honest, not much
in the way of potential here.
是吗？我刚失去六个夜行者
Yeah, well,
I just lost six Nightwalkers.
我得填补空缺
I got holes to fill.
我速战速决
你们感到渴望
I'll keep this quick.
That itch you feel?
是吸血的需求越加强烈
That's the need to feed
coming on strong.
渴望吸食人血
A hunger for human blood.
你就成为吸血鬼
你就会再死一次
Drink it, you're a vampire,
don't, you die. Again.
这次是永久的，死在这运尸袋里
This time, for good.
Right here, in a body-bag.
你想留下谁？
漂亮傻女孩还是同志好友？
Hey, what do you think?
Cute, dorky girl or gay best friend?
你来选吧
Dealer's choice.
我来选，好吧
Dealer's choice, okay.
捡到这枚硬币的人得永生
Whoever picks up this coin
gets to live forever.
另一个人就得死
The other one dies.
开始
Go.
该死，女孩，真该死
(LAUGHS)
Damn, girl! I said, damn!
你怎么能这样？
How could you?
好了，乔许，我别无选择
Get over it, Josh.
It's not like I had a choice.
你也会这么做的
但你是个软弱的小…
You would've done the same thing,
but you're such a little weak--
让她在坟墓里自生自灭吧
Let her die in cold storage.
背叛朋友就是这个下场
Got a thing about people
who betray their own friends.
走吧，我们去兜个风
Come on.
Let's go for a ride.
走吧
Go.
好，就这样
All right.
That's it.
让我看看你还有什么本事
Tell me what else you've got.
触剑攻击，换反防守
Attaque au fer!
Now, counter-parry.
击中，明显击中了
A hit!
Palpable hit.
有朝一日我要娶你
I'm gonna marry you, someday.
我才不会嫁个决斗时打不过我的人
I would never marry someone
who couldn't best me in a duel.
再来一局吗？
Another lesson?
蕾贝卡米卡森
Rebekah Mikaelson.
又来教我击剑了吗？
Come to teach me another lesson?
我上次见你时，皇家卫起火了
你们全逃出城
Last time I saw you, Royal Street
was burning and you all were fleeing
躲避父亲追赶
the city from your daddy.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
你从未回来确认过
You never looked back to find out.
你来这里干什么？
Why are you here?
找以利亚
我觉得克劳斯对他做了什么
Elijah. I think Klaus
has done something to him.
好了，别说了
Stop, stop, right there.
从你们米卡森家族身上我学到一点
There's one thing I learned
about you Mikaelsons.
不要卷进家族斗争
It's don't get in the middle
of family feuding.
没有好下场
It doesn't end well.
我们之间什么也没发生
我以生命担保
There's nothing going on between us,
I swear it, on my life.
你的生命对我很重要
Your life means something to me.
跟我说实话
否则情况将大不相同
Give me the privilege of honesty,
or that will cease to be the case.
我喜欢她，我觉得她也喜欢我
I like her, and I think it's mutual.
但我什么都没做，我不会的
But I haven't done
anything about it and I wouldn't.
- 除非…
- 将来也不会
-Not if--
-And you won't.
我爱我妹妹，但她总是遇人不淑
I love my sister, but she lacks
fortune when it comes to men.
他们来来去去，只有我一直都在
They come and go for her.
But I am the constant.
她是我的家人
She's my family.
你说过我也是家人
Well, you said I was family.
我求过你把我变成吸血鬼
I have begged you to
turn me into a vampire.
我说过当你准备好我就会转变你
And I told you,
I will turn you when you're ready.
你再靠近蕾贝卡，就永远别想转变
You go near Rebekah again,
and you never will be.
即使你已功成名就，你还是怕他
Even after all you've achieved,
you're still scared of him.
我不怕任何人
No, I'm not scared of anyone.
要是我发现你知道以利亚的下落
If I find out
you know where Elijah is...
你就不用怕克劳斯了
我会亲手干掉你
...you needn't fear Klaus.
I'll kill you myself.
虽然念及旧情，但是我帮不了你
Nostalgia's a blast and all,
but I can't help you.
还是很高兴见到你
It's nice seeing you though.
但愿你能找到你要的
Good luck finding
what you're looking for.
我懂那个表情，是和女人有关
I know that face.
Woman trouble.
你这个混蛋，你知道是吧？
You're a dick, you know that?
为什么不告诉我你妹妹回来了？
Why didn't you tell me your
sister's back in town?
我觉得让你自己发现不是更有意思嘛
I thought it'd be more amusing
for you to find out for yourself.
还有什么瞒着我吗？
Anything else that I need to know?
就是她这一百年来变得越发神经
Only that she's grown considerably
more insane in the last century.
也许就是她杀了我的人
Or maybe that it was her
who killed my guys.
难说，除非那个飙车族酒吧
经常有土里土气的
Doubtful. Unless that biker bar
is frequented by small-town,
高中橄榄球四分卫光顾
不然她才没那个兴趣
high school quarterbacks,
I can't imagine she'd be interested.
喂？
Yeah.
刚收到消消，有人在毕恩维尔公园
发现一个狼人
MAN: Just got a tip. Someone saw
a werewolf in Vionville Park.
带几个夜行者把他逮住
Get a couple Nightwalkers
to run it down.
把他的脑袋给我带回来
Bring me back its head.
看来杀了那几个喽罗的凶手
也水落石出了
Well, I guess that solves the
mystery of the murdered riff-raff.
至少我妹妹是清白的
Least my sister's in the clear.
关于那事，我可没时间
搅和你们的米卡森家庭剧
About that, I don't have time
for Mikaelson family drama.
你是我的客人，管好你妹妹
You're my guest,
keep your sister in line.
我用一支吸管把密西西比河吸干
还比较有可能
I'd have greater chance of draining
the Mississippi with a straw!
来吧，海莉
Come on, Hayley.
就肚子痛一下
这愚蠢的一切就都结束了
One upset stomach and all this
stupid drama is ancient history.
到法语区来真是个愚蠢的行为
Dumb move comin' into the Quarter.
跟我走吧，狼人
You're comin' with me, wolf.
我在这里已经受够了你们吸血鬼
告诉我该做什么
I have had it up to here with
vampires telling me what to do!
啊！
Ah!
这样对待孕妇可不好
Now, that is no way
to treat a pregnant lady.
我真的很讨厌没礼貌的人
I do hate bad manners.
这就是我叫你不要离开屋子的原因
This is why I told you
never to leave the house.
法语区是禁止狼人出入的
Werewolves are banned in the Quarter.
我本来计划好了，但你晚上出去
小蹦达一圈就危及到整个形势
I had a plan and your little stroll
put it all in peril.
别管他
Leave him!
你已经管得够多了，不觉得吗？
You've done enough,
don't you think?
把这些尸体像路标一样丢在我门前
Leaving a trail of bodies
like a roadmap to my door.
要不是我无意间听到取狼人脑袋的事
If I hadn't overheard this lot
bragging about werewolf heads,
这里每一个人都完蛋了
everyone here would be screwed.
还有别跟我扯什么计划
And don't give me that
crap about having a plan.
你一直都有时间去执行你的计划
You've had all the time
in the world to execute a plan
但你什么都没做出来
and no one's seen
you do a damn thing.
以利亚做了个交易来保护你的孩子
Elijah made a deal
to protect your child
希望能把你从自私堕落的
自我中拯救出来
so that he could save you
from your selfish, rotten self.
而你显然根本不在乎这个孩子和以利亚
But you obviously don't give a damn
about the child or Elijah,
瞧你做了什么去珍惜这一切？
because what have
you done to honor it?
我做了一切
I have done everything.
要我一件件地跟你讲清楚吗？
Let me spell it out for you,
shall l?
从我到这的第一天，马赛尔就不信任我
From the day I arrived,
Marcel hasn't trusted me.
从第一天开始
他竞让他的吸血鬼服下有毒的马鞭草
From day one, he's had his
vampires ingest toxic vervain,
而你知道的，妹妹
那是用来防止他们受我精神控制
which, as you know, little sister,
protects them from my mind control.
我需要一个间谋
I needed a spy.
一个和我里应外合
且马赛尔永远不会怀疑的人
Someone on the inside, with me,
who Marcel would never suspect.
所以我赶在他之前先下手为强
So, I created a day zero
and got there first.
嘿
Hey!
拜你大开杀戒所赐
马赛尔失去了六个吸血鬼
Marcel had just lost six vampires,
thanks to your little murder spree
他急需招募新人
and he needed new recruits.
好
Okay.
所以我把其中一个变成我的人
在他一滴马鞭草都没进之前
KLAUS: So I made the new one mine
before he'd had even a drop of vervain.
现在我们来聊聊你可以为我做什么
Let's have a little chat
about what you can do for me.
但我们都知道真正获得一个男人的信任
是要获取他的心
But we all know the real way
to a man is through his heart.
于是…
So.
我兄弟马赛尔…
不错的小伙子，你不觉得吗？
My mate, Marcel.
Nice bloke, don't you think?
不
No.
他很迷人、性成、自信、充满魅力
He's charming, sexy,
confident, incredibly hot.
但老实说，他是个坏小子
But let's be honest,
he's a bad boy, right?
跟你一样
Like you.
而现在我需要一个好男人
而不是一个…
And right now, I only need
good in my life, not someone who's--
被不幸的伤害，不再完整
无法摆脱自己心魔的人？
Tragically wounded and damaged
by demons he can't escape?
那些受伤的人
不是合适的对象
The damaged ones,
they're not good.
至少对我来说不是
At least, not for me.
我懂，真的懂
I understand, I do.
不管怎样，给他一次机会
However, give him one chance.
然后我需要你告诉我他去了哪里
见了谁
Then, I need you to tell me
where he goes and who he sees.
而这家伙
我会排干他体内的马鞭草
And this one.
I'm gonna drain him of vervain.
魅惑他相信他的兄弟找到了自己的信仰
搬去了犹他州
Compel him to believe his mates
found religion and moved to Utah,
这样他就能向马赛尔解释
为什么今晚又损失了三个吸血鬼
so that he can explain to Marcel
why he lost three more vampires tonight.
你们还有什么问题吗？
Does anyone have
any more questions?
没有？很好
因为我有个问题
No? Good.
Because I have a question.
海莉
首先，你在该死的法语区
Hayley, what were you doing,
in the bloody French Quarter,
干什么？
in the first place?
- 回答我
- 别管她了
-Answer me!
-Leave her be.
你想知道我干了什么？
You wanna know what I was doing?
我买了毒药
这样就可以让你的小宝贝解脱了
I was buying poison. So I could put
your little baby out of its misery.
尼克
Nik!
放开她
看在老天的份上，她怀孕了
Keep your hands off her,
she is pregnant for God's sake!
所有关于不想要这个孩子的威吓
All of this bluster
about not wanting the child,
当她说准备好不要这个孩子的那一刻…
and then the second she tells
you she's ready to get rid of it....?
在意一个人没什么大不了的
It's okay to care.
想得到一些东西很正常
It's okay to want something.
这就是以利亚一直在努力的
这就是他对你的期望
That's all Elijah was trying to do,
all he's ever wanted for you.
也是我们一直想要的
All we've ever wanted.
我把以利亚交给了马赛尔
I gave Elijah to Marcel.
什么？
What?
马赛尔很紧张
Marcel was nervous.
一个真祖回来就很难对付了
更别说两个
Bad enough one Original
return to town, but two?
他的手下变得坐立不安
His crew was getting antsy.
他想要以利亚消失
所以我给了他一个和解的提议
He wanted Elijah gone,
so I gave him a peace offering.
你竟然拿我们的哥哥做交易
You bartered our brother.
我有计划
I have a plan.
得到马赛尔的信任，消灭他的帝国
Gain Marcel's trust,
dismantle his empire,
实现以利亚希望孩子出生的心愿
honor Elijah's wish
that that baby be born.
我的计划只有我自己清楚
I am executing that plan
the only way I know how.
如果你不喜欢
随时可以离开
If you don't like it,
there's the door.
看我在不在意
See if I care.
我知道你不怎么了解我，但还是谢谢
I know you don't know me very well,
but thanks.
非常感谢你刚才的举动
I appreciate what you did in there.
我们女孩不就应该互相照顾
Us girls have got to
look out for each other.
你们俩怎么了？
What is it with you two?
你说过你恨他
但你对待他的方式再明显不过了
You say you hate him, but the way
you deal with him it's so clear.
即使你恨他，你还是爱着他
Even when you hate him,
you still love him.
我想当你和一个人生活了千年
I guess when you spend
a thousand years with someone,
决定离开的时候
就像丢掉了自己的一部分
deciding to quit them is
like losing a part of yourself.
但有时这份恨意实在太强烈了
But sometimes the hate
is just so powerful.
被克劳斯杀掉的男朋友不只艾米尔一人
Emil wasn't the only boyfriend
of mine that Klaus killed.
他一次又一次地这么做
每当我找到心爱的人
He did it again and again, every
time I found someone to care about.
他就把对方杀死
直到我终于不再坠入爱河
He just kept doing it until,
finally, I stopped falling in love.
他说这是为了保护我，不让我犯错
He said he was protecting me
from my mistakes,
没有人能配得上他妹妹
that no one was ever good enough
for his little sister.
直到有一天他的出现
Until one day, someone was.
河水怎么样？
How was the river?
很凉爽，清甜
It was cool, sweet.
我该去…
I should go talk--
- 我哥哥会杀了你的
- 那我会笑着死去
-My brother will kill you.
-Then I'll die smiling.
我不是警告过你了吗？
Did I not warn you?
克劳斯，我求求你
他跟别人不一样
Klaus, I beg of you!
He's not like any other.
你第一眼见他时就知道了
You saw it in him
from the very first day.
你救了他
保护他
You saved him.
Protected him.
你抚养他长大
You raised him.
你不忍心杀他的
You cannot kill him.
你说得对
我不忍心
You are right, I cannot.
但是你，我亲爱的妹妹
But you, dear sister,
需要好好地上一课，让你懂得
不要随便抢走属于我的东西
need a lesson in what you can
and cannot take from me.
如果你知道以利亚在马赛尔手上
为什么不自己去把他救回来？
If you know Marcel has Elijah, why
don't you just get him back yourself?
因为如果激怒了我哥哥
我就会躺在楼下那个
Because if I cross my brother,
there's still a coffin downstairs
写着我名字的棺材里了
with my name on it.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我在你棺材底下找到的
I found them under your coffin.
如果这几把古董牛排刀
是唯一能阻止你
So, if a couple of antique steak
knives were the only thing stopping
救回以利亚的东西
那么你拿去吧
you from getting Elijah back,
then, here you go.
我让大家都提前下班了
I sent everyone home for the night.
今晚就让我来为你服务吧
I am your humble host.
好吧
风度翩翩加一分
Well, okay.
Extra points for flare.
美好的夜晚才刚开始
And the night's just started.
是什么让你决定赴约？
What made you decide to come?
每个人都值得有一次机会
Everyone deserves a chance.
你骗了我
我哥哥在哪里？
You lied to me.
Where's my brother?
你也好啊
卡蜜，这是蕾贝卡，蕾贝卡，这是卡蜜
Hello to you too.
Cami, Rebekah. Rebekah, Cami.
看得出你仍然对金发妞情有独钟
I see you still have
a thing for blondes.
嘿
Hey!
告诉我以利亚在哪
Tell me where Elijah is.
到底发生了什么事？
What the hell is going on?
告诉我他在哪，不然我杀了你
Tell me where he is
or I will kill you!
不，你不会的
No, you won't.
或许你说得对
Perhaps you're right.
但我会杀了她
But I will kill her.
放开她
你赢了
Let her go.
You won.
我带你去见以利亚
I'll take you to see Elijah.
你们到底是什么人？
What the hell are you people?
嘘…没事的
回家
Sh.... It's okay.
Go home.
忘了这一切，只要记得我会
好好补偿你的，我向你保证
Forget all this and just know that
I will make it up to you. I promise.
你想见以利亚？
好，跟我来
You want to see Elijah?
Fine, follow me.
邀请我进去
Invite me in.
那得问问屋子的女主人
黛维娜
Gotta ask the lady
of the house, Davina.
出来吧，亲爱的
Come on out, sweetheart.
邀请她进来
Invite her in.
请进
Come in.
我可不会这么做
I wouldn't do that.
你到底是谁？
Who the hell are you?
黛维娜
Davina.
她是真祖之一是不是？
She's an old one, isn't she?
没错，蕾贝卡是真祖
Yeah.
Rebekah is an Original.
也就是说她是杀不死的
Which means she can't be killed.
她好像也不太友善
She doesn't seem very nice.
她可以的
She can be.
只是今晚她对我不太好
But she hasn't been
very nice to me tonight.
那恐怕是时候送客了
Then I'm afraid
it's time for you to leave.
是时候了
Well, it's about time.
我都等得不耐烦了
I was bored waiting.
但又万般期待看到你的表情
因为绝对有趣
But I did so want to see your face
and it is, indeed, priceless.
你这混蛋
今天星期几？
You bastard.
What day is it?
星期天
Sunday.
我被匕首插了一个礼拜？
I have been daggered
for a whole week?
马赛尔，你把他怎么了？
Marcel, what have you done to him?
现在是1887年，蕾贝卡
It's 1887, Rebekah.
你被匕首插了52年
You've been daggered
for 52 years.
什么？
What?
不用担心马赛尔
我给了他一个选择
And don't worry about Marcel,
I presented him with a choice.
他可以选择拔掉你的匕首
和你共渡他
He could choose to undagger you and
live out the rest of his human days
- 凡人的余生，或是
- 不
-with you or....
-No.
我如他所愿把他变成吸血鬼
....I could turn him,
instead, as he's always wanted,
只要他放弃你
in exchange for giving you up.
不，他不会那么对我
No.
He wouldn't do that to me.
他放弃了
Oh, but he did.
欢迎回来，蕾贝卡
MARCEL: Welcome back, Rebekah.
你昏过去好一会儿了
You were out for quite a while.
我在哪里？
Where am l?
我怎么会在这里？
How'd I get here?
你惹恼黛维娜了
You upset Davina.
真高兴你们俩终于见面了
I'm glad you two finally got to meet.
现在你很清楚自己是跟谁做对了
Now, you know what
you're dealin' with.
这是我原来的房间
Is this my old room?
现在是我的了
It's mine, now.
就像这个城市是我的，黛维娜是我的
以利亚也是我的
Just like this town is mine,
Davina's mine and Elijah's mine,
直到我想放了他为止
until I feel like giving him back.
从前属于你，属于你哥的
现在都是我的了
What was once yours, what was
once your brother's, it's now mine.
还有不许再碰卡蜜
And don't ever touch Cami again.
我没喝那个
I didn't use it.
你醒了
You're awake.
我几乎整晚没睡
I could barely sleep all night.
这房子活像是沼泽地里的桑拿房
This house is like
a freaking swamp sauna.
你怎么放弃了？
What stopped you?
你本来可以摆脱这一切的
You could've been
free of all of this.
摆脱我
Of me.
是啊，不过在我击退那些吸血鬼时
Yeah, well, when I was
fighting off those vampires,
我发觉我不光是在保护自己
I realized I wasn't
just protecting myself.
也许是因为我的亲生父母
遗弃了我
Maybe it has to do with the fact
that my birth-parents gave me up
而养父母又把我赶出家门的关系
and my adopted parents
kicked me out.
我只知道到了紧要关头
All I know is, push came to shove
我才意识到我不能让他受到丝毫伤害
and I realized
I wouldn't let anyone hurt it.
我开始觉得我们是同病相怜，你和我
I'm beginning to think
we're a lot alike, you and l.
我们都是被逼到走投无路时
We're both cast-offs
who've learned to fight
学会了反抗的废物
when we're backed into a corner.
我们已经被逼到走投无路了
Well, we're backed
into a corner now.
可不是
That we are.
是时候反抗了
It's time to fight...
小狼
...Little wolf.
和马赛尔之间的所有事
你和女巫的约定
This whole thing with Marcel,
the deal you have with the witches,
试图扳倒他，夺走他的一切
trying to take him down,
take what's his....
蕾贝卡告诉我
你和他曾像一家人那样相亲相爱
Rebekah told me that you two
once loved each other like family.
出什么事了？
What happened?
我造就了今日的马赛尔
I made Marcel everything that he is.
待他如亲生儿子
I treated him like a son.
但一百年前我父亲从纽奥良追杀我
And when my father chased me
and my family from New Orleans,
和我的家人的时候
我们以为马赛尔被杀了
a hundred years ago,
we believed Marcel was killed.
我们以各自的方式悼念了他
We each mourned him in our own way.
但当我再度归来
我才发现他不只是活了下来
Yet, when I returned,
I found not only had he survived,
还过得很好
he had thrived.
没想过要找到我们
也没想过要团结有如一家人
Instead of seeking us out,
instead of sticking together as one,
他选择了夺走我家族建立的一切
he made a choice to take
everything my family had built
据为己有
and make it his own.
如今他住我们的房子
睡在我们的床上
Now, he is living in our home,
he is sleeping in our beds.
他到处张贴“M”
That "M" he stamps everywhere....
这个M不是代表马赛尔
It's not for 'Marcel'.
它代表的是米卡森
it's for 'Mikaelson.'
我要夺回一切
I want it all back.
如果我得除掉他才能成功
And if I have to
push him out to get it,
那我正有此意
then that's exactly what I'll do.
我去找人来看看空调
I'll have someone see
to the air conditioning.
你说得对
You were right.
那个叫卡蜜的女孩是关键
The girl, Cami, she's the key.
马赛尔喜欢她，也因为如此
Marcel likes her and because of that,
我才见到了你总念念不忘的
他的秘密武器
I got to see this secret weapon of his
that you've been going on about.
那就别兜圈子了
是什么东西？
Well, don't stand on ceremony.
What is it?
不是东西，是人
一个叫黛维娜的女孩
It's not a "what", it's a "who."
A girl, Davina.
她不会超过16岁
我也从未成受过那样强大的力量
She can't be more than sixteen
and I've never felt power like that.
一个女巫
A witch.
她不是随便哪个女巫
她绝对是我前所未见
She's not just any witch.
She's something I've never seen before.
强大得无法估量的女巫
Something beyond powerful.
而且拜你所赐，以利亚在她手上
And now, because of you,
she has Elijah.
谁知道她能对他做什么
Who knows what she could do to him?
她在什么地方？
Where is she?
那个狡猾的小贱人
That clever bitch.
我不知道
I don't know.
怎么回事？
What's wrong?
她把我对那个地点的记忆抹去了
She wiped my memory of the location.
马赛尔拥有一个
比真祖更法力无边的武器
Marcel possesses a weapon bigger
and more powerful than an Original
你却把我们的哥哥拱手给了他
and you handed our brother to him!
以利亚到底要原谅你多少次？
How many times will
Elijah forgive you?
到底还要多久他才会对
希望你得到救赎死心？
How long until his hope for
your redemption finally dies?
我是逼不得已的
I did what I had to do!
马赛尔抢走了我们的房子
Marcel took our home!
这房子没有家人就一文不值
And our home is worthless
without family.
我会找到以利亚
I am finding Elijah.
不计任何代价
Whatever it takes.
你会帮我吗？
Are you going to help me?
不计任何代价
Whatever it takes.
刚才的不愉快我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that unpleasantness.
她吓不了我
She doesn't scare me.
没人可以
None of them do.
我知道没人可以，亲爱的
I didn't think they would, honey.
但问题是，他们好像想留下
But the thing is,
it seems like they're here to stay.
他们不属于这里
They don't belong here.
要说服他们这一点恐怕不太容易
It might be kinda tough
to convince them of that.
所以我想请你帮个忙
Which is why I need to
ask you for a favor.
我希望你去弄清楚
我们怎样才能杀死真祖
I'm gonna need you to figure
out how we kill an Original.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）